so what music do I play people have been
asking uh when do I play it where do I
find it Well the answer is right here on
the
Spotify um I will provide links to these
things here but if you do exclamation
point music in the chat which I'll do
right now you can see my tiny we just
started I'm doing I'm sneaking this in
before something else happens so you do
music there that'll show you link you
can get the Spotify link you can also do
exclamation point song and that'll give
you the current song so let's let's go
through what the different ones
are so This spol Grass uh Cafe chill is
more more you know French cafe kind of
stuff my 80s this is mostly New Wave um
alternative uh it's got all kinds of
good stuff in there dark rage is really
harsh actually um a lot of people might
not like that that's actually one of my
most favoritest ones for when we do
hacking uh yoga Beach concert is the one
that I play probably the
most um and this this is like upbeat
yoga music uh yoga chill Ang soong is
probably my favorite this is a 20 minute
it's perfect for shasana by the way
um but we got all kinds of stuff there
uh it's probably going to you know it's
a good Chill song hacker chill is going
to be the most common one when you're
doing open when we're doing
co-working you know it it's Mr Robot
pretty much you're probably already
going to get demonetized just for that
those are my main playlists that's it so
folk Grass Cafe chill 80s dark rage yoga
Beach concert and yoga chill uh when are
we going to play them so people ask they
like what when is the music going to be
on what day um honestly there's really
no set day for any particular music uh
it just depends on what my mood is but
you will always get uh yoga chill during
yoga time um that's really the only
thing I can promise you everything else
is pretty random so that's where you can
get the music if you want it